Paulo Canedo C. Rodrigues

Brazilian | paulocanedo@gmail.com | https://github.com/paulocanedo

Software Developer

Graduated in Computer Science and a Specialization course in Mobile Development. Experience in desktop and web applications development using open source technologies. Loves the profession and keep learning a little bit every day. The area which is more fascinated is about computer graphics with OpenGL followed by desktop application.

Technical Skills

Main Languages: JavaScript, Java, C++

Other Languages: PHP, C, Python, Objective C, lisp

Operation Systems: Linux, OSX, Windows

Database: MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB

Professional Experience

2011 to Present - Tribunal de Justiça do Tocantins

Worked on a desktop application that view and sign (with e-token) PDF documents; web search jurisprudence with apache solr; Maintenance of the major company application dealing with apache http, nginx, php, java, mongodb, linux server

2010 to 2011 - FCAS Organização Inteligente de Documentos

Participated in developing a Java desktop application that scans and management access to physical documents

2008 to 2009 – Tribunal de Contas do Estado do Tocantins

Contributed in developing an application (web and desktop) that analyses the public managers accounts

2007 to 2008 - REDESAT Tocantins

2006 to 2007 - CREA-TO

Education & Certifications

Bachelor of Computer Science - Universidade Federal do Tocantins — Palmas, Brazil Specialization course in Mobile Development - Faculdade Catolica do Tocantins — Palmas, Brazil Sun Certified Java Programmer 1.6 Interactive Computer Graphics with WebGL — Coursera Online